

ABILITIES

- Programming knowledge
- Self-taught
- Teamwork
- Proactive

LANGUAGES

- Português Nativo
- Inglês Intermediário

KNOWLEDGE

- Python Flask, DJango, Selenium
- **⊘** C# ASP.NET Core
- JavaScript jQuery
- HTML, CSS
- SQL MySQL
- WordPress
- Git GitHub

VICTOR G. RAMOS

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



(61) 99539-6398 victorgrferreira@gmail.com https://ka-konata.github.io



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a self-taught Full Stack developer with knowledge of various languages and technologies in software development. I have programming skills in Python, JavaScript, C#, and PHP, and I am proficient in technologies such as ASP.NET Core, Flask, Django, discord.py, Selenium, and jQuery. I also have experience with HTML, CSS, WordPress, SQL, and MySQL.

EXPERIENCE

Loja Mundi

Trainee • Jul 2022-Feb 2023

- Trainee for an indefined period in the area of Information Technology and Marketing.
- I helped with the development of marketing strategies, web design, articles translation and the development of web systems for the company.

Inovitec Contabilidade

Freelancer | Web Developer • Jun 2021-Jun 2022

- I worked for 3 hours a day developing an Ecommerce website at WordPress platform.
- I acquired some knowledge in the PHP language and improved my skills with JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

System Analysis and Development

Universidade Paulista • 2022-2023 • Currently at 4° Sem.

- Requirements Analysis and Gathering.
- Software Engineering.
- Programming/Systems Development.

PROJETOS PESSOAIS

API RestFull using ASP.NET Core

Set 2023 • College work • link

Python Library for APIs Integration

Dez 2022 • Related to a ChatBot project. • link